Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Assistant Files, 1965-2011; III.
  - Mark Carmel, 1980-2004; 6.
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1996 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Consulting Engineers Council, 2001 (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania covered bridge funding, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, PENNDOT, 1998-1999 (Box 376, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, PENNDOT highway funds, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Public Transportation Association (PPTA), 2001 (Box 376, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Route 202, 2003 (Box 376, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Route 309 Project, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Route 422/Krick Lane intersection improvements, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Route 611 Project, 2004 (Box 376, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania state transportation funding cuts, 1996 (Box 376, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Training Institute, Bus safety training (Box 376, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania transit operators, 1999 (Box 376, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Pennsylvania Turnpike, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Philadelphia baseball stadium project, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Philadelphia International Airport radar/automation interruptions, 2000 (Box 376, Folder 20-21)
    - Transportation, Philadelphia International Airport STARS Radar System, 2002 (Box 376, Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Pike County transportation issues, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 23)
    - Transportation, John G. Pinto Federal Railroad Administration nomination, 2001 (Box 376, Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International Airport, 1998-2002 (Box 376, Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International airport, Busway project, 1995-1999 (Box 376, Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International Airport, FAA Engingeering Center Proposal, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International Airport, Privatization, 1996 (Box 376, Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International Airport, Radar outages, 1996 (Box 376, Folder 29)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh International Airport, Terminal demolition, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 30)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh North Shore/Central bus district improvement program, 1999 (Box 376, Folder 31)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh Port Authority, 2000-2001 (Box 376, Folder 32)
    - Transportation, Pittsburgh Regional Renaissance Partnership, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 33)
    - Transportation, Port Authority of Allegheny County (PaTransit), 1997-2003 (Box 376, Folder 34)
    - Transportation, Port Erie ferry landing, 1996 (Box 376, Folder 35)
    - Transportation, Power Superconductor Program applicants (Box 376, Folder 36)
    - Transportation, Public transportation federal fundng issues, 1995-2001 (Box 376, Folder 37)
    - Transportation, Rail warehousing, 2002 (Box 376, Folder 38)
    - Transportation, Railroad Competition Act, 2003 (Box 376, Folder 39)
    - Transportation, Railroad regulation, 1999 (Box 376, Folder 40)
    - Transportation, Railroad rehabilitation legislation, 2001 (Box 376, Folder 41)
    - Transportation, Railway Services Corporation, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 42)
    - Transportation, Ravensburg Bridge Project, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 43)
    - Transportation, Reading Regional Airport, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 44)
    - Transportation, Reagan National Airport Bill, 1998 (Box 376, Folder 45)
    - Transportation, Reflector tape and tractor-trailer safety, 1998 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Robinson Town Centre, 1999 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Robinson Town Centre Pittsburgh Intermodal Complex, 1997 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Rouse Estate, Youngsville, 1997-1999 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 22, Monroeville to Mundy's Corner Project, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 30, Lancaster, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 202, 2002-2004 (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 219, 1997 (Box 377, Folder 8-9)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 220, Clearfield, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 222, Berks County, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 291, Chester, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 322, Clarion/Verango County, 1998 (Box 377, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, U.S. Route 366, Westmoreland County, 1996 (Box 377, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Safe, Sober Streets, 1998 (Box 377, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Schoolhouse Lane, Philadelphia improvement project, 1998 (Box 377, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Schuylkill River Park Project, 1999 (Box 377, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Schuylkill Valley metro project, 2000-2001 (Box 377, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Scranton to New York rail service, 1999-2000 (Box 377, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Senior Citizen transportation services, 2003 (Box 377, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA), 1996-2000 (Box 377, Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, January-July 2001 (Box 377, Folder 22-23)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, September 2001 (Box 377, Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, October, October 2001 (Box 377, Folder 25-27)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, December 2001 (Box 377, Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, December 2001 (Box 378, Folder 1-3)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, January, 2002 (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Specter v. Surface Transportation Board, Hollidaysburg Car Shop Info, 2001 (Box 378, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Spring Township transportation improvement district, 1998 (Box 378, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Stourbridge Rail Line, Honesdale, 2003 (Box 378, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Strategic rail finance, 1997-1998 (Box 378, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Sumneytown Pike Forty Foot Road reconstruction project, 1997 (Box 378, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Surface Transportation Board reauthorization, 1999 (Box 378, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Towanda Borough transportation commerce facility, 1997 (Box 378, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Traffic.com, 2001-2002 (Box 378, Folder 12-14)
    - Transportation, Trans World Airlines, Flight 800, 1996-1998 (Box 378, Folder 15)
    - Transportation,TransBridge and Lehigh Valley Thruway bus connection, 1998-1999 (Box 378, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Transit issues, 1993-1995 (Box 378, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Transit tax credit, 2000-2001 (Box 378, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Transportation Coalition, 1996-1999 (Box 378, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Union Pacific/Southern Pacific merger, 1996 (Box 378, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, United Airlines, 2002 (Box 378, Folder 21)
    - Transportation, United Airlines/US Airways merger, 2001 (Box 378, Folder 22-24)
    - Transportation, United Airlines/US Airways merger, 2001 (Box 379, Folder 1-3)
    - Transportation, UP U.S. to China air service, 1999 (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, United Switch and Signal Company railway safety issues, 1998 (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, US Air, Erie jet service, 2001-2002 (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, US Air, Flight 427 accident, 1995 (Box 379, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, US Airways, 1997 (Box 379, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, US Airways, 2002 (Box 379, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Aircraft maintenance and training center, Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 379, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, US Airways, Erie jet service, 2002 (Box 379, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, US Airways, Pension issue, 2003 (Box 379, Folder 12-13)
    - Transportation, US Airways, Philadelphia to Italy nonstop service, 1996-1998 (Box 379, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Venango County Regional Airport, 1997-1998 (Box 379, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Venango County Regional Airport and Essential Service Program, 2001 (Box 379, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Washington Air Route Traffic Control Center (ZDC), 2001 (Box 379, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Washington County Airport, 1989-1992 (Box 379, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Westmoreland County Airport, 1998-2001 (Box 379, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Wilkes Barre/Scranton Airport, 1998 (Box 379, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Wilkes Barre/Scranton Airport radar tower upgrades, 1993 (Box 379, Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Wilkes-Barre Intermodal Transportation Center, 2002-2003 (Box 379, Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Williamsport/Lycoming Airport, 1998 (Box 379, Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Williamsport Regional Airport, I-80 ramp project, 1997 (Box 379, Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Wings Field extension project, Montgomery, 2001 (Box 379, Folder 25)
    - Transportation, York Township transportation issues, 1999 (Box 379, Folder 26)
    - Treasury and Postal, 1995 (Box 379, Folder 27)
    - Treasury and Postal, Legree S. Daniels, Postal Service Board of Governors nomination, 1998-1999 (Box 379, Folder 28)
    - Treasury and Postal, S. David Fineman, Postal Service Board of Governors nomination, 1998-1999 (Box 379, Folder 29)
    - Treasury and Postal, John B. Kelly, Jr. commemorative postage stamp, 2000 (Box 379, Folder 30)
    - Treasury and Postal, Lehigh Postal Encoding Center, 1999 (Box 379, Folder 31)
    - Treasury and Postal, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1995-1997 (Box 379, Folder 32)
    - Treasury and Postal, National Association of Postal Supervisors, 1997-2001 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Treasury and Postal, National Association of Postmasters of the United States, 1996-2004 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Treasury and Postal, National League of Post Masters, 1996-1998 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Treasury and Postal, Pennsylvania Rural Letter Carriers Association, 2001 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Treasury and Postal, Peter J. McCloskey Postal Facility, Pottsville, 1997 (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - Treasury and Postal, Philadelphia postal properties and development, 1996-2001 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Treasury and Postal, Postage stamp issues, 1997-1999 (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - Treasury and Postal, Postal Financing Reform Act, 1997 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - Treasury and Postal, Postal Service Auto Day Program, 1998 (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - Treasury and Postal, Postal Service Core Business Act, 1997-1998 (Box 380, Folder 10)
    - Treasury and Postal, Postal Uniform Allowance Program, 1997-1998 (Box 380, Folder 11)
    - Treasury and Postal, Reese Brothers mail rate issue, 1995-1998 (Box 380, Folder 12)
    - Treasury and Postal, Ed Satell Progressive Business Publications and Postal Inspection Service, 1996-1998 (Box 380, Folder 13-14)
    - Treasury and Postal, Scranton Federal Courthouse, 1995 (Box 380, Folder 15)
    - Treasury and Postal, Six Day mail delivery, 2001 (Box 380, Folder 16)
    - Treasury and Postal, Throop Borough zip code issues, 1996 (Box 380, Folder 17)
    - Treasury and Postal, U.S. Post Office Equal Opportunity Employment investigation, 1993 (Box 380, Folder 18)
    - Treasury and Postal, USPS, 1997-1999 (Box 380, Folder 19)
    - Treasury and Postal, USPS, Facility projects freeze, 2001 (Box 380, Folder 20)
    - Treasury and Postal, USPS, Five-year strategic plan, 2001-2005 (Box 380, Folder 21)
    - Treasury and Postal, USPS, Inspection service, 2000-2001 (Box 380, Folder 22)
    - Treasury and Postal, Willow Grove Post Office, 2002 (Box 380, Folder 23)
    - Treasury and Postal, Wyndmoor Post Office, 1996 (Box 380, Folder 24)
  - Kevin Carpenter, 1981-2007; 7.
    Kevin Carpenter served as: staff assistant, 2003; and legislative correspondent, 2004-2007.
    - 1099 employment issue, Background, 2005-2006 (Box 380, Folder 25)
    - 1099 employment issue, Slippery Rock University, 2005-2006 (Box 380, Folder 26)
    - 1099 employment issue, Specter response, 2006 (Box 380, Folder 27)
    - Business files, 2005-2006 (Box 380, Folder 28-29)
    - Business files, Business requests, 2004 (Box 380, Folder 30)
    - Business files, Companies, 2004-2006 (Box 380, Folder 31)
    - Business files, Estate tax, 2006 (Box 380, Folder 32)
    - Business files, Hedge funds articles, 2006 (Box 380, Folder 33)
    - Business files, ITC steel pipe hearing, 2005 (Box 380, Folder 34)
    - Business files, Kardex, 2006 (Box 380, Folder 35)
    - Business files, Kastel, 2006 (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - Business files, Letters of recommendation, 2003-2006 (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - Business files, Letters on legislation, 2005-2006 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - Business files, Meetings, 2004-2006 (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - Business files, Mergers, 2005-2006 (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - Business files, National Council of Social Security Management Associations, 2007 (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - Business files, National Taxpayers Advocate, 2006 (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - Business files, Norman Rosenthal, 2004 (Box 381, Folder 8)
    - Business files, Wachovia branch closings, Philadelphia, 2006 (Box 381, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Buck letters, 2004-2006 (Box 381, Folder 10-12)
    - Correspondence, Constituent letters, 2004-2006 (Box 381, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence, DC, Business and banking, 2004 (Box 381, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, DC, Tax, Pensions and economic, Thank-yous, 2004 (Box 381, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, DC, Telecommunications, 2004-2005 (Box 381, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, General, Busines and banking, 2004-2006 (Box 381, Folder 18-19)
    - Correspondence, General, Steel, 2003-2006 (Box 381, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, Tax, telecommunication, oensions and economic, Social Security, 2005-2006 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Pennsylvania, Business and banking, 2004-2006 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Pennsylvania, Tax, Telecommunication, Pensions and economic thank yous, 2003-2005 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Pennsylvania, VIP mail, 2003-2006 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, To-do, 2003-2004 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Uncategorized, 2004-2006 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - Office, Fax file, 2003-2005 (Box 382, Folder 7-8)
    - Office, Meeting log, 2003-2004 (Box 382, Folder 9-11)
    - Office, Meeting notes, 2006 (Box 382, Folder 12)
    - Office, Notebooks, 2003-2006 (Box 382, Folder 13-15)
    - Office, Specter memos, 2003-2006 (Box 382, Folder 16)
    - Office, Specter memos, 2003-2006 (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Steel, 1994-1998 (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - Steel, American Iron and Steel Institute, 1995 (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - Steel, Case studies, 1999 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - Steel, Caucus, 1993-1995 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - Steel, Caucus, 1995 (Box 383, Folder 6-7)
    - Steel, Caucus, 1995-1998 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - Steel, Caucus, 1996 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - Steel, Caucus, June-October, 1998 (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - Steel, Caucus, November-December, 1998 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - Steel, Caucus, 2003-2004 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - Steel, Caucus, Becker testimony, 1995 (Box 383, Folder 13)
    - Steel, Caucus, CUSP legislative conference, 1998 (Box 383, Folder 14)
    - Steel, Caucus, First meetings, 1993 (Box 383, Folder 15)
    - Steel, Caucus, Hearing, 1999 (Box 383, Folder 16)
    - Steel, Caucus, Issues, 1998 (Box 383, Folder 17)
    - Steel, Caucus, S. 332, 1993 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - Steel, Caucus, Ways & Means Subcommitee, 1999 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Steel, Companies, 1990-1993 (Box 384, Folder 3-4)
    - Steel, Company files, Associations, 1998 (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - Steel, Company files, Individual, 1998 (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - Steel, GATT compliance, 1994 (Box 384, Folder 7)
    - Steel, International Trade Commission case filing, 1996 (Box 384, Folder 8)
    - Steel, Korean steel, 1999 (Box 384, Folder 9)
    - Steel, Korean War crimes, 2002 (Box 384, Folder 10)
    - Steel, Korean War crimes review US Army, 2001 (Box 384, Folder 11)
    - Steel, News, 1998-1999 (Box 384, Folder 12)
    - Steel, Pension and benefits, 2002 (Box 384, Folder 13)
    - Steel, Presidential report on steel, 1999 (Box 384, Folder 14)
    - Steel, Private Right of Action (PRA), 1998 (Box 384, Folder 15)
    - Steel, PRA, Legal analysis, 1998 (Box 384, Folder 16)
    - Steel, PRA, Revised tariffs, 1999 (Box 384, Folder 17)
    - Steel, Russian dumping, 1999 (Box 384, Folder 18)
    - Steel, S. 21 Antidumping, 1998 (Box 384, Folder 19)
    - Steel, S. 121, Foreign steel, 1998 (Box 384, Folder 20)
    - Steel, S. 332, PRA, 1993-1995 (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Steel, Specialty steel industry in US, 1993-1994 (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - Steel, Steel amendment to Emergency Supplemental Appropriations, 1999 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - Steel, Trade Act of 1974, Section 301, 1998 (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - Steel, Trade Fairness Act (TFA), 1998 (Box 385, Folder 5-6)
    - Steel, TFA, 1999 (Box 385, Folder 7)
    - Steel, TFA, Proposal, 1999 (Box 385, Folder 8)
    - Steel, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, 1999 (Box 385, Folder 9)
    - Steel, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Congressional Record, 1999 (Box 385, Folder 10)
    - Steel, Voluntary Restraint Agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 385, Folder 11-14)
    - Steel, Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel, 1998 (Box 385, Folder 15)
    - Steel, White House correspondence, 1998 (Box 385, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Congressional Record, 1981-1999 (Box 385, Folder 17)
    - Tax, Congressional Record, 1987-1994 (Box 385, Folder 18)
    - Tax, Tax shelter hearing, Evidence and testimonies, 2003 (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Tax shelter hearing, Exhibit and witness lists, 2003 (Box 386, Folder 2-3)
    - Tax, Tax shelter industry report and newsclips, 2003 (Box 386, Folder 4)
    - Votes, Antitrust, Banking and bankruptcy, 1982-1991 (Box 386, Folder 5)
    - Votes, Business, 1983-2000 (Box 386, Folder 6)
    - Votes, Budget and copyright, 1981-1999 (Box 386, Folder 7)
    - Votes, Minority issues, Product liability, Securities, Small business, and Social Security, 1981-1995 (Box 386, Folder 8)
    - Votes, Steel and telecommunications, 1981-1999 (Box 386, Folder 9)
    - Votes, Tort reform, Medical malpractice and others, 1984-1995 (Box 386, Folder 10)
    - Votes, Tort reform, Medical malpractice and others, 1996-2001 (Box 386, Folder 11)
  - Jennifer Castagna, 1993-2008; 8.
    Jennifer Castagna served as: legislative correspondent, 2000-2001; and legislative assistant (appropriations, childcare, economic development, education, housing, urban affairs, welfare), 2002-2009.
    - Abstinence education, 2007-2008 (Box 386, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture appropriations, 2007 (Box 386, Folder 13)
    - Americorps, 1995-2000 (Box 386, Folder 14)
    - Appropriations, 1993 (Box 386, Folder 15)
    - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 386, Folder 16)
    - Appropriations, 2007 (Box 386, Folder 17)
    - Appropriations earmarks, 2007 (Box 386, Folder 18)
    - Appropriations memos, 2007 (Box 386, Folder 19)
    - Association of Independant Colleges and Universities, 1999 (Box 386, Folder 20)
    - AT&T/Comcast merger, 2000-2002 (Box 386, Folder 21-23)
    - Binge drinking, 1999-2000 (Box 386, Folder 24)
    - Albert Boscov, 1999-2001 (Box 386, Folder 25)
    - Commerce and Justice appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 1)
    - Continuing resolution, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - Defense appropriations, 2008 (Box 387, Folder 3)
    - Echostar/DirectTV merger, 2002 (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - Ed-Flex, 1999 (Box 387, Folder 5)
    - Education budget, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 6)
    - Election reform, 2000-2001 (Box 387, Folder 7-10)
    - Energy appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 11)
    - Dwight Evans, 2001 (Box 387, Folder 12)
    - Financial Services markup, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Operations appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 14)
    - General Services Administration, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 15)
    - Goals 2000, 1994-1995 (Box 387, Folder 16)
    - Higher education, 1997 (Box 387, Folder 17)
    - Hispanic Task Force, 1999 (Box 387, Folder 18)
    - Hope VI grants, 2000-2001 (Box 387, Folder 19)
    - Homeland Security appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 20)
    - Hospitals, Universities, Businesses and Schools, 2001 (Box 387, Folder 21)
    - Hotel Casey, 1999 (Box 387, Folder 22)
    - Housing and Urban Developement appropriations, 1997 (Box 387, Folder 23)
    - Housing and Urban Development appropriations, 1998 (Box 387, Folder 24)
    - Housing and Urban Development requests, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 25)
    - Interior appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 26)
    - Labor, Health and Human Services markup, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 27)
    - Lead hazard control, 2000 (Box 387, Folder 28)
    - Legislative Branch appropriations, 2007 (Box 387, Folder 29)
    - Memos, 1998-2000 (Box 387, Folder 30)
    - Microsoft Settlement, 2001 (Box 387, Folder 31)
    - Microsoft Settlement, 2001 (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - Military Construction and Veterans Affairs appropriations, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - Millennium Committee, 1999 (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - Monitoring former welfare recipients, 1999 (Box 388, Folder 4)
    - Tim Murphy, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 5)
    - Napster, 2000-2001 (Box 388, Folder 6-7)
    - National Night Out, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 8)
    - Office on National Drug Control, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 9)
    - Omnibus Conference Agreement, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania defense appropriations, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia blight, 2001 (Box 388, Folder 12)
    - PRIME Act, 1999 (Box 388, Folder 13)
    - Prisoner education, 2000-2001 (Box 388, Folder 14)
    - Project HOME, 2000 (Box 388, Folder 15)
    - Public Safety Officers Educational Assistance ACt, 1997 (Box 388, Folder 16)
    - Restoring Earnings to Lift Individuals and Empower Families Act, 2001 (Box 388, Folder 17)
    - Sanctuary cities, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 18)
    - School violence, 1999 (Box 388, Folder 19)
    - Tax bill, 1999 (Box 388, Folder 20)
    - Tax cut, 2003 (Box 388, Folder 21)
    - Tax legislation, 2001 (Box 388, Folder 22-24)
    - Transportation appropriations, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 25)
    - United Mine Workers, 2007 (Box 388, Folder 26)
    - United/US Airways merger, 2000-2001 (Box 388, Folder 27-28)
    - United/US Airways merger, 2000-2001 (Box 389, Folder 1-3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Housing and Urban Development and Independent Agencies Bill, 2002 (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers, 1997-2000 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - YouthBuild, 2000 (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - Andy Cobula, 1992-1994; 9.
    Andy Cobula worked in Senator Specter's office, with materials dated 1992-1994.
    - Economic recovery, 1992 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - World Cup Commemorative Coin Bill, 1994 (Box 389, Folder 8)
  - Allison DeKosky, 1975-2008; 10.
    Allison DeKosky served as: legislative correspondent, 1997; legislative aide, 1998; and legislative assistant, 1999-2002.
    - Healthcare, Consolidation in the Pennsylvania health insurance industry, Articles, 2008 (Box 389, Folder 9)
    - Healthcare, Consolidation in the Pennsylvania health insurance industry, Correspondence, 2007 (Box 389, Folder 10)
    - Healthcare, Consolidation in the Pennsylvania health insurance industry, Memos, 2008 (Box 389, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare, Consolidation in the Pennsylvania health insurance industry, Senator Specter's opening statement and talking points, 2008 (Box 389, Folder 12)